<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bowl on Surfskate Location Guide by Denise</title>
    <link>https://denisenepraunig.github.io/tags/bowl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bowl on Surfskate Location Guide by Denise</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 05:32:49 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://denisenepraunig.github.io/tags/bowl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Skatepark Gleisdreieck Bowls Berlin - Germany</title>
      <link>https://denisenepraunig.github.io/posts/skatepark-gleisdreieck-bowls-berlin-germany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 05:32:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denisenepraunig.github.io/posts/skatepark-gleisdreieck-bowls-berlin-germany/</guid>
      <description>Inside Gleisdreieck Park in Berlin, there are various skate locations. Therefore, make sure to double-check when you Google the location to find the one with the bowls. The &amp;ldquo;Green Waves&amp;rdquo; is another interesting spot in that area, but it will be covered in a different blog post.
There are two bowls. The smaller one has coping all around, while the bigger bowl features a deep end, a love seat, a cradle, and a roll-in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skatepark Poststadion Berlin - Germany</title>
      <link>https://denisenepraunig.github.io/posts/skatepark-poststadion-berlin-germany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 03:33:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denisenepraunig.github.io/posts/skatepark-poststadion-berlin-germany/</guid>
      <description>Opened in 2017, the Skatepark inside Poststadion Berlin offers a combination of a bowl and a street section. The bowl comes equipped with coping, and its height varies, allowing you to gradually increase the challenge from a small drop-in on the quarter pipe to bigger drop-ins on the opposite side. In addition to this, the bowl features two roll-ins, so you can safely build up some speed without having to drop in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skatepark Berlin Bernau - Germany</title>
      <link>https://denisenepraunig.github.io/posts/skatepark-berlin-bernau-germany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 01:13:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denisenepraunig.github.io/posts/skatepark-berlin-bernau-germany/</guid>
      <description>The Bernau Skatepark features a bowl, segmented into sections with and without coping, complimented by a roll-in. Additionally, it offers a street section equipped with a quarter-pipe and a bank. The skatepark was build by Populär Skateparks in 2017. During my visit to the skatepark last year, I unfortunately didn&amp;rsquo;t have my surfskate with me, so I&amp;rsquo;m unable to provide specific insights into the rideability of the bowl. However, the park was new at the time and I did observe the concrete was impressively smooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camacrew Skatepark Berlin Buch - Germany</title>
      <link>https://denisenepraunig.github.io/posts/camacrew-skatepark-berlin-buch-germany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 16:38:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denisenepraunig.github.io/posts/camacrew-skatepark-berlin-buch-germany/</guid>
      <description>The Berlin Buch Skatepark, which opened in 2020, features both a bowl and a street section. The bowl is fully equipped with coping around its perimeter, and the site is pleasantly surrounded by lush greenery and trees.
The street section incorporates a half-size bowl, an ideal spot for practicing drop-ins without the intimidating height of the full bowl. Not far from there, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a smaller quarter pipe - another great piece to practice drop-ins.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
